Finding Aid for the Collection of Research Materials Related to Linguistic-Psychological Studies of Genie (pseudonym), 1895-2003, 1970-2003 LSC.0800
UCLA Library Special Collections
- 8. Research, ca. 1938-1994 (bulk 1970-1977)
  - 8H. Testing, 1969-1975
    - Playtest--Overview of therapist-controlled mini-computer system, 1974 August 22 (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Playtest--Notebook entries, 1974 October 13-22; 1977 May 8 (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - Material sent by Andrea Thompson from University of California Santa Barbara, 1974 October 14 (Box 78, Folder 14)
      Regarding Bobby Klatzky material.
    - Results of various diagnostics and evaluations administered to Genie, 1975 January-April; 1976 January 31 (Box 78, Folder 15)
    - Recognition activity--notes, 1975 April 17 (Box 78, Folder 16)
    - Results of language test administered by L. Solow in sign only, 1975 June (Box 78, Folder 17)
    - Colors, objects, numbers, letters, 1975 June 26 (Box 78, Folder 18)